const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'Who is Scabbers?',
        answer1: `Harry's Owl`,
        answer2: `Hagrid's Dog`,
        answer3: `Ron's Rat`,
        answer4: `Neville's Frog`,
        correctAnswer: `Ron's Rat`
    },
    {
        question: `What is Luna Lovegood's house?`,
        answer1: 'Gryffindor',
        answer2: 'Ravenclaw',
        answer3: 'Hufflepuff',
        answer4: 'Slytherin',
        correctAnswer: 'Ravenclaw'
    },
    {
        question: `Harry's patronus takes the shape of what animal?`,
        answer1: 'Otter',
        answer2: 'Doe',
        answer3: 'Stag',
        answer4: 'Terrier',
        correctAnswer: 'Stag'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many horcuxes does Voldemort have?',
        answer1: 5,
        answer2: 7,
        answer3: 9,
        answer4: 11,
        correctAnswer: 7
    },
    {
        question: 'Which ball must be caught to end a quidditch match?',
        answer1: 'Snitch',
        answer2: 'Bludger',
        answer3: 'Quaffle',
        answer4: 'Gobstone',
        correctAnswer: 'Snitch'
    },
    {
        question: `Who guarded the entrance to the Sorcer's Stone hiding place?`,
        answer1: 'Fang',
        answer2: 'Buckbeak',
        answer3: 'Norbert',
        answer4: 'Fluffy',
        correctAnswer: 'Fluffy'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is Remus Lupin?',
        answer1: 'Vampire',
        answer2: 'Werewolf',
        answer3: 'Ghost',
        answer4: 'Goblin',
        correctAnswer: 'Werewolf'
    },
    {
        question: `Which animal's feather is in Harry's wand?`,
        answer1: 'Phoenix',
        answer2: 'Harpy',
        answer3: 'Swan',
        answer4: 'Jobberknoll',
        correctAnswer: 'Phoenix'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where was Harry born?',
        answer1: 'London',
        answer2: 'Diagon Alley',
        answer3: 'The Burrow',
        answer4: `Godric's Hollow`,
        correctAnswer: `Godric's Hollow`
    },
    {
        question: 'What is also know as the Come and Go Room?',
        answer1: 'The bathroom',
        answer2: 'The Room of Requirement',
        answer3: 'The Great Hall',
        answer4: 'The Gryffindor common room',
        correctAnswer: 'The Room of Requirement'
    }
]